Irving Berlin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-219)
  - Watch your step, Stage, 1914
    - Lock me in your harem and throw away the key, Alternate title: Lock me in your harem and throw the key away; Dropped during rehearsals
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/11)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With holograph annotations (Box-folder 207/11)
    - The minstrel parade
      - Sketches; [6] p. (Box-folder 207/12)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/12)
    - Move over
      - Manuscript lead sheets; [1, 1] p. (Box-folder 207/13)
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 207/13)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 207/13)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/13)
    - Musical demon
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/14)
    - Office hours, Alternate title: Opening chorus; Typewriter song; Entrance of relatives
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/15)
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 207/15)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 207/15)
    - Opera burlesque scene
      - Manuscript lead sheet-Sextette section; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/16)
      - Manuscript lead sheet-Rigoletto section; [2] p., Laid in: sketch for "When I'm in love" (Box-folder 207/16)
      - Sketches; [6] p. (Box-folder 207/16)
      - Sketch for Madam Butterfly section; [3] p. (Box-folder 207/16)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; 5 leaves (Box-folder 207/16)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/16)
    - Play a simple melody see also Miscellaneous lyric sheets from Say it with music, Alternate title: A simple melody
      - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 207/17)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/17)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 207/17)
    - Ragtime opera medley, Alternate titles: Old operas in a new way; Finale Act II-opera medley
      - Typescript cue sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/18)
    - Settle down in a one-horse town
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/19)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/19)
    - Show us how to do the fox-trot
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/20)
    - The syncopated walk
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/21)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/21)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/21)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 207/21)
    - There's a fire burning down in my heart, Not used
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/22)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/22)
    - There's a girl on my mind see also Non-show music, Not used
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/23)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/23)
    - They always follow me around
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/24)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 207/24)
      - Printed piano-vocal score; p. 4-48, From printed songbook (Box-folder 207/25)
    - They're dancing teachers, Not used
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/26)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/26)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/26)
    - Watch your step
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 207/27)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/27)
      - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With holograph annotation (Box-folder 207/27)
    - What is love?
      - Manuscript/typescript vocal part; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/28)
    - When I discovered you
      - Manuscript piano score; [1] p. (Box-folder 207/29)
      - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/29)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 207/29)
    - When I get back to my hometown, Not used
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 207/30)
      - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 207/30)
      - Carbon copies of typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 207/30)
      - Photocopies of typescript and manuscript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 207/30)
      - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Revised lyrics for Irving's 50th birthday in 1938, renamed "When you get back to my home town", alternate title "Give my regards to Hiram Brown the grocery man" (Box-folder 207/30)
    - When it's nighttime in Dixieland see Non-show music
    - When I'm in love see also Opera burlesque scene, Not used
      - Sketches(2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 207/31)
      - Photocopy of sketch; [1] p., Photocopied from verso of Madam Butterfly from Opera Burlesque (Box-folder 207/31)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 207/31)
  - White Christmas, Film, 1954
    - Scores and parts
      - Bound condensed score; [481] p. (Box-folder 208/1)
      - Bells see also Ziegfeld follies of 1920
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 208/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 208/2)
      - The best things happen while you're dancing
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 208/3)
        - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 208/3)
        - Copyist's manuscript parts; [24] p., Transparencies in folder; Conductor, piano, voice, A-B violins, C violins, viola, cello, 3rd clarinet, bass clarinet, 2nd trumpet, 1st trumpet, 1st clarinet, 2nd clarinet, 3rd trumpet, 2nd trombone, 1st trombone, bass, drums, guitar, and photocopies of bass clarinet, cello and 2 drum parts; On folder: girl vocal, F (Box-folder 208/3)
        - Copyist's manuscript parts; [21] p., Transparencies in folder; Conductor, piano, voice, A-B violins, C violins, viola, cello, 3rd clarinet, bass clarinet, 2nd trumpet, 1st trumpet, 1st clarinet, 2nd clarinet, 3rd trumpet, 2nd trombone, 1st trombone, bass, drums, guitar, and photocopy of piano-vocal score (with annotations); On folder: boys key (Box-folder 208/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal scores; 2 p. each, 3, 1 with annotations (Box-folder 208/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 208/3)
      - Choreography
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/1)
        - Sketch of manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 209/1)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 209/1)
      - Count your blessings instead of sheep
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies; On folder: girls key of G, G to A; Laid in: copyist's manuscript parts (transparencies); [21] p. (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Sketches; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); 3 p., Laid in 1 copy: typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Holograph lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Manuscript lyric sheet (Helmy Kresa); [1] p. (Box-folder 209/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [11] leaves (Box-folder 209/2)
      - A crooner, a comic, Not used; Earlier version: A singer, a dancer; Adapted from Monohan and Callahan
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., At top: version for Crosby and O'Connor (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p., Incomplete, with annotations (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal score; 3 p., With annotations (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal score; [5] p., No lyrics, with annotations (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal score(2); 3 p. each (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Printed piano-vocal scores(2); [5] p. each (Box-folder 209/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 209/3)
      - Gee, I wish I was back in the Army
        - Manuscript full score; 11 p. (Box-folder 28/9)
        - Manuscript conductor score; 3 p. (Box-folder 28/9)
        - Manuscript parts (Box-folder 28/9)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/4)
        - Sketches; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/4)
        - Photocopy of piano-vocal score; [1] p., With annotations (Box-folder 209/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 209/4)
      - How does a pilot spend his furlough, Not used; Same music as What does a soldier want for Christmas?; this version originally intended for Sayonara
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., Vocal only (Box-folder 209/5)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., Original title is crossed out: What does a soldier want for Christmas (Box-folder 209/5)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves (Box-folder 209/5)
      - I'd rather see a minstrel show
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 209/6)
      - Love, you didn't do right by me
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/7)
        - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 209/7)
        - Copyist's manuscript parts, Transparencies; On folder: boy key, G, C# to D (Box-folder 209/7)
        - Copyist's manuscript parts, Transparencies; On folder: girl key, D, G# to A (Box-folder 209/7)
        - Photocopies of printed piano-vocal score(2); [2] p. each (Box-folder 209/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 209/7)
      - The old man see also If we weren't married from Stars on my shoulders, Earlier title: (We'll follow) the old man
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Sketches of piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Sketches; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Photocopies of manuscript piano-vocal scores; 3, 2, 2 p. (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Printed piano-vocal scores(2); [3] p. each (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Holograph signature (Box-folder 209/8)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [6] leaves (Box-folder 209/8)
      - Sisters
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p., Chorus only (Box-folder 209/9)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/9)
        - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [2] p., Laid in: sketch of piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 209/9)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 209/9)
        - Printed piano-vocal scores(2); [2] p. each (Box-folder 209/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 209/9)
      - Snow see also Free from Call me madam
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/10)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 209/10)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Laid in: manuscript piano-vocal score (incomplete); [1] p.; Original title crossed out at top: Free (Box-folder 209/10)
        - Photocopy of typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, Copied from bottom of lyric sheet, for original see The most (Box-folder 209/10)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 209/10)
      - What can you do with a General?, Originally written for Stars on my shoulders
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Sketch of piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p., Laid in: sketch of piano score; [1] p.; Laid in: typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves, With holograph annotations (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves (Box-folder 209/11)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); [5] p. each (Box-folder 209/12)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/12)
        - Photo negative of manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 209/12)
        - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 209/12)
        - Sheet music, Without cover (Box-folder 209/12)
      - What does a soldier want for Christmas?, Music later used for How does a pilot spend his furlough?
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., No lyrics (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Photocopies of piano-vocal score; 7 p. each, 2, 2 copies each (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Photocopy of copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 7 p. (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 209/13)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves, Some with annotations (Box-folder 209/13)
      - When it's night time in Dixie land see also Non-show music, Originally written for Watch your step
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p., Transparencies (Box-folder 209/14)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 209/14)
    - Scripts
      - Carbon copies of typescript story notes for White Christmas(3); 7 p. each (Box-folder 210/1)
      - Mimeograph & carbon copies of typed script; [235] p., Black binder; Laid in: photocopy of researcher's notes on contents of the binder; [1] leaf (Box-folder 210/2)
      - Mimeograph & carbon copies of typed script; [202] p., Black binder; Laid in: photocopy of researcher's notes on contents of the binder; [1] leaf (Box-folder 211/1)
      - Mimeograph & carbon copies of typed script; [179] p., Black binder; Laid in: photocopy of researcher's notes on contents of the binder; [1] leaf (Box-folder 211/2)
  - Wise guy see also The last resorts, Unproduced, 1956; Apparently based on Cleveland Amory’s 1952 book, Last resorts; the earlier title, The last resorts, was the first of Berlin’s two attempts to write a musical about brothers Wilson and Addison Mizner; the second attempt, 4 years later, was based on Alva Johnson’s The legendary Mizners, and first entitled Sentimental guy, and later, Wise guy.
    - Scores and parts
      - Anybody can write see Mr. President
      - Card sense
        - Sketches; [4] p. (Box-folder 212/1)
        - Typescript lyric and script sheets; [13] leaves (Box-folder 212/1)
      - Dallas/I like New York, Sung separately and then together in counterpoint
        - Sketches; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/2)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [10] leaves (Box-folder 212/2)
      - Gold
        - Sketches; [3] p., Laid in: typescript song list; [1] leaf (Box-folder 212/3)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves, Some with annotations (Box-folder 212/3)
      - Go home and tell it to your wife, Alternate title: You can't do this to me
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/4)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/4)
        - Photocopy of manuscript piano-vocal score; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/4)
        - Holograph lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 212/4)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 212/4)
      - I never want to see you again
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., With "patter", incomplete (Box-folder 212/5)
        - Sketches; [4] p. (Box-folder 212/5)
        - Typescript lyric sheet; [1] leaf, With shorthand annotations (Box-folder 212/5)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 212/5)
      - It takes more than love to keep a lady warm
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 212/6)
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 212/6)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves, One sheet with holograph annotations (Box-folder 212/6)
      - Klondike Kate
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 212/7)
        - Sketch; [3] p. (Box-folder 212/7)
        - Typescript lyric sheetes; [5] leaves (Box-folder 212/7)
      - Love leads to marriage see Say it with music
      - Love is for boys
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves, At bottom: Dec. 13th, 1955, dictated over phone from hospital (Box-folder 212/8)
      - Opening the Mizner story, Alternate titles: Three more minutes to midnight (opening); Two more minutes to midnight (opening chorus)
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p. (Box-folder 212/9)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/9)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [7] leaves (Box-folder 212/9)
      - The snobs on the wrong side of the tracks see also The last resorts
        - Manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 212/10)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/10)
        - Holograph lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 212/10)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [10] leaves (Box-folder 212/10)
      - You'd make a wonderful wife for some man
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [4] leaves (Box-folder 212/11)
      - You're a sentimental guy
        - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., With annotations (Box-folder 212/12)
        - Copyist's manuscript piano-vocal scores(2); 4 p. each (Box-folder 212/12)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/12)
        - Manuscript lyric sheet; [1] leaf (Box-folder 212/12)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [5] leaves (Box-folder 212/12)
      - You're a sucker for a dame, Alternate title: I'm a sucker for a dame
        - Sketch of piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 212/13)
        - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 212/13)
        - Typescript lyric sheets; [8] leaves, Some with holograph annotations (Box-folder 212/13)
    - Scripts/miscellaneous
      - Typed draft of script; [67] leaves, Red folder; Laid in (front cover): photocopies of the following songs and typescript lyrics: Mizner story, a typescript list of 11 songs and a reprise for Act I and 4 songs; Opening chorus, description of setting, 3 choruses and tag, 1/5/56; Card sense, chorus, 4/12/56; Love leads to marriage - chorus, 3/5/56; I’m gonna get him - verse and 2 choruses, 3/5/56; You’re a sucker for a dame - verse and 2 choruses, 11/28/55; The snobs on the wrong side of the tracks - one chorus only, 11/29/55; You’re a sentimental guy - verse and 2 choruses, 12/4/56; I never want to see you again - chorus, patter, second chorus, 4/10/56; Anybody can write - 2 pages, verse and 3 choruses, 2/10/56; Is she the only girl in the world? - chorus, 5/5/54 (Box-folder 212/14)
      - Typed scripts; 29, 12, 32 p., Bound; On t.p.: Sentimental guy (tentative title) (Box-folder 212/15)
      - Typed script and carbon copy; 13 p. each, Stapled; On t.p.: Musical play based on Alva Johnston's The legendary Mizners (Box-folder 212/16)
      - Typed script; 18 p., Stapled, two loose pages; This is an alternate version of previous (Box-folder 212/16)
      - Typescript synopsis of second act with carbon copy; [1] p. each, Manuscript on top: Dec. 1956 (Box-folder 212/16)
      - Typescript/carbon song lists and miscellaneous; [10] leaves, Manuscript note on Irving Berlin memo paper: interesting correspondence re Mizner story in 1956 Abe Berman file (Box-folder 212/17)
  - Yip, Yip, Yaphank, Stage, 1918
    - Bound manuscript piano-vocal score; [47] p., On cover: Original manuscript of Yip yip yaphank presented to Paul Block by his friend the author and composer Irving Berlin (Box-folder 213/7)
    - Bevo see Ziegfeld follies of 1919
    - Come along, come along, come along see Ziegfeld follies of 1920, Alternate title: Floradora sextette
    - Ding dong, Originally written for The canary, 1918
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 213/8)
      - Manuscript orchestral parts (Box-folder 214/1)
    - Down from the follies see Miscellaneous lyric sheets, Alternate title: Follies opening
    - Dream on, little soldier boy
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 213/9)
    - Ever since I put on a uniform, Alternate title: What a difference a uniform will make
      - Manuscript orchestral parts (Box-folder 214/2)
    - I can always find a little sunshine in the YMCA, Alternate title: The YMCA
      - Manuscript lead sheets (2); [4] p. each (Box-folder 213/10)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 3 p. (Box-folder 213/10)
    - Kitchen police (poor little me) see also This is the Army
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p. (Box-folder 213/11)
      - Manuscript orchestral parts (Box-folder 214/3)
    - Kiss me, sergeant see Miscellaneous lyric sheets, Not used
    - Love interest, Alternate title: Love interest (I love you)
      - Full score; 10 p. (Box-folder 213/1)
    - Mandy
      - Full score; [23] p. (Box-folder 213/2)
    - Oh! How I hate to get up in the morning Alexander's ragtime band and This is the Army now
      - Photocopies of piano-vocal score(2); [6] p. each, Inscription by Irving Berlin to Mrs. J.F. Bell (Box-folder 213/12)
      - Fair copy (Kresa) manuscript piano-vocal score; 4 p. (Box-folder 213/12)
      - Photocopies of typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 213/12)
    - Opening act
      - Full score; 35 p. (Box-folder 213/3)
    - Overture
      - Full score; [11] p. (Box-folder 213/3)
    - Page boys
      - Sketch; [1] p., On verso: untitled cello part marked in ink with the name "Dan Coslas" (Box-folder 213/13)
    - Ragtime razor brigade
      - Full score; 11 p. (Box-folder 213/4)
      - Manuscript lead sheets; [2, 1] p. (Box-folder 213/14)
      - Sketch; [2] p. (Box-folder 213/14)
      - Photocopies of typescript lyric sheets; [2] leaves (Box-folder 213/14)
    - Send a lot of jazz bands over there, Alternate title: Jazz land
      - Full score; [24] p., Laid in: manuscript lead sheet (chorus only); [1] p. (Box-folder 213/5)
      - Manuscript lead sheet; [3] p. (Box-folder 213/15)
    - The sterling silver moon see Mandy, Alternate title: Under the sterling silver moon
    - We live at Upton with Major General Bell, Alternate title: General Bell song
      - Photocopies of lead sheet(2); [1] p. each, At top: violin part (Box-folder 213/16)
      - Photocopies of manuscript lyric sheet(2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 213/16)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] leaves (Box-folder 213/16)
    - We're on our way to France
      - Full score; 10, 11 p. (Box-folder 213/6)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal scores; 3, [3] p. (Box-folder 213/17)
      - Sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 213/17)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Manuscript conductor lead sheets; [28] p. (Box-folder 213/18)
      - Manuscript conductor lead sheets; [32] p., In folder; On cover: conductors score, P.F.C. Siegel (Box-folder 213/18)
      - Typescript lyric sheets (Box-folder 213/19)
        - Follies opening; Ragtime razor brigade; Kiss me Sergeant; [2] leaves
        - Soldier boy; Bevo; My country 'tis of thee; Mandy; Y.M.C.A.; [1] leaf
        - When we got back to the USA; [1] leaf
        - Finale of Act II, scene 1; [5] leaves
    - Manuscript orchestral parts by instrument
      - Flute (Box-folder 214/4)
      - Oboe (Box-folder 214/5)
      - Clarinet 1 (Box-folder 214/6)
      - Clarinet 2 and 3 (Box-folder 214/7)
      - Bassoon (Box-folder 214/8)
      - Horn (Box-folder 215/1)
      - Trumpet 1 (Box-folder 215/2)
      - Trumpet 2 and 3 (Box-folder 215/3)
      - Trombone (Box-folder 215/4)
      - Tuba (Box-folder 215/5)
      - Drum (Box-folder 215/6)
      - Violin 1 (Box-folder 216/1)
      - Violin 1 (second stand) (Box-folder 216/2)
      - Violin 2 (Box-folder 216/3)
      - Violin 2 (second stand) (Box-folder 216/4)
      - Bass (Box-folder 216/5)
      - Extra flute (Box-folder 216/6)
      - Extra clarinet (Box-folder 216/7)
      - Extra bassoon (Box-folder 216/8)
      - Extra horn (Box-folder 216/9)